"迷失" 前情提要...
Previously on "Lost"...
James 你说过 你在那里
When you were over there, James, you mentioned that
看到Widmore派人 守着他潜艇上的一个房间...
Widmore had someone guarding a room on his submarine...
- 是因为 他有东西不想让你看到?  - 嗯 怎么了?
- guarding something he didn't want you to see?  - Yeah. So?
我讨厌神秘兮兮的
I don't like secrets.
你说 你把我带回这个岛
You told me you brought me here to the island
是来做大事的 什么时候动手?
to do something important. When do we tart?
你走吧
Run.
这些人很危险
These people are extremely dangerous.
我们得马上动身
We need to go now.
带路吧
Lead the way.
这人想离开小岛的话
This man wants to leave the island,
只能依靠飞机
and that plane's the only way he can do it.
你不是想知道我们该去干嘛么? 我们去阻止他
Do you wanna know where we're going? We're gonna stop him.
- 怎样能阻止他登机?  - 毁掉飞机
- How you gonna stop him from getting on that plane?  - We have to destroy it.
当今世界充满争议
In a world of conflict and strife,
唯一例外的只有...
there is but one fact we all can agree upon...
人人爱Hugo
Everybody loves Hugo.
尽管出身贫寒
Born to humble surroundings,
Hugo Reyes却像明灯一样
Hugo Reyes has always been a beacon of light
照亮了身边所有人
for all who crossed his path.
Hugo爱吃鸡
Hugo's lifelong love affair with chicken
由此开创了"咯咯鸡"快餐店 并将连锁店
led him to acquire and then expand the Mr. Cluck's chain
开遍全世界
into a worldwide phenomenon.
Hugo取得的一系列成功
The exponential growth of Hugo's success
令人惊叹
was startling.
但他的成功 并非仅仅局限于财富方面
But financial success wasn't the end,
它有着更广泛的含义
it was the beginning.
Hugo成了
Hugo and giving
"慈善"一词的代言人...
became synonymous...
公园...
Parks...
游乐场...
Playgrounds...
医院...
Hospitals...
"咯咯鸡"儿童乐园
The Mr. Cluck's house for children.
这些各式各样的慈善机构...
The philanthropy was unparalleled...
令我们今夜有幸共聚一堂
which brings us to this evening
见证Hugo Reyes位于加州历史博物馆的
and the opening of the Hugo Reyes Paleontology Wing
古生物分区开馆...
at the Golden State Natural History Museum...
这是我市最伟大的善人之一
A lasting beacon of culture
为我们带来的
that bears the name
永恒的文化之光
of one of our city's greatest benefactors.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
欢迎我们的
our man of the year...
年度大使Hugo Reyes!
Hugo Reyes!
喔!
Whoo!
这奖杯真有个性 对吧?
It's a pretty cool trophy, huh?
- 嗯 Hugo  - 对了 下周六晚 还有人文基金在等着我们
- Mm-hmm, Hugo.  - Oh, you know we got the human fund next Saturday night.
- 没问题吧?  - 又一座奖杯收归囊中
- Can you make it?  - Another trophy.
人人爱Hugo
Everybody loves Hugo.
你知道有谁不爱么?
You know who doesn't?
女人
Women.
妈!
Ma!
你得找个女人 过后半辈子
You need a woman in your life,
除了把屎把尿 把你带大的女人外
especially one who has not nursed you.
真恶心
That's disgusting.
我忙得半死 没空找女人
And I'm too busy to meet someone.
你不是忙得半死 你是怕得半死
You're not too busy. You're too scared.
我才不怕
I'm not scared.
- 不怕就好 因为你明天有个约会  - 和谁约会?
- Good, because you have a date tomorrow.  - I do?
Tito爷爷邻居的女儿 Rosalita
Grandpa Tito's neighbor's daughter, Rosalita.
她答应和你共进午餐
She agreed to lunch with you.
她想干嘛?
What's she like?
- 想见你啊  - 妈
- Willing to meet you.  - Ma.
去见她!
You're going!
她会爱上你的
She's gonna love you.
如果她没爱上你
And if she doesn't,
我们迟早也能找到个爱你的人
we will find someone who does.
最近发生了很多疯狂的事
A lot of crazy stuff's been happening.
我真希望能当面和你谈谈
I kinda wish I could talk to you about it in person.
很多人跑来找我说话 可他们已经...
A lot of people have come to talk to me after they've...
死了
you know, gone.
如果你也能来找我 那该多好
It would be nice if you could, too.
Hugo啊?
Hugo?
你走不走?
You guy to go?
等我一回来 我们就动身
Once I'm back, we're leaving.
- 你要去哪儿?  - "黑岩洞"
- Where you going?  - "The black rock."
如果要炸飞机 我们就得先搞到炸药
If we're gonna destroy that plane, we'll need dynamite.
你确定要这样做?
You sure that's the right move?
不确定 但只能这么做
No. But it's the only move we have.
嗯 你看着办吧
Well, you're the expert.
这是谁的墓?
Whose grave is this?
她叫Libby
Her name was Libby.
当时她坐在机尾
She was in the tail section of the plane.
那是我们的第一次约会
We were gonna have our first date.
我们本打算去野餐
It was gonna be, like, a picnic.
但...
But...
没多久 她就遇害了
then she was murdered.
真遗憾
I'm sorry.
嗯 我也这样觉得
Yeah, me, too.
嘿
Hey.
你在这儿干嘛?
What are you doing here?
我来 是为了阻止你害死大家
I'm here to stop you from getting everyone killed.
迷失 第6季第12集
你无话可说么?
You gonna say something?
我凭什么相信你?
Why should I trust you?
你杀了Libby和Ana Lucia
You murdered Libby and Ana Lucia.
现在这些无关紧要
That doesn't matter right now.
重要的是 你们想到岛的另一头
What matter is you going across the island
去引爆飞机? 大家都会死的...
to blow up that plane? People are gonna die...
死这么多人 责任全在你
A lot of people, and it's gonna be your fault.
什么?
What?
因为大家现在都听你的 Hurley
Because people are listening to you now, Hurley.
Hurley啊
Hurley.
你在跟谁说话?
Who are you talking to?
呃...
Um...
没谁
No one.
走吧
Come on.
我们该走了
We're leaving.
我帮您再拿些手工玉米粉圆饼片 怎样?
Can I get you some more homemade tortilla chips?
好的 去拿吧
Sure. Whatever.
呃 这些先别收 好吗?
Uh, can you leave those?
我在等人
I'm meeting someone.
她稍后就到
She's running late.
好的 圆饼片马上就给您送来
Right. Chips are on the way.
你是Hugo?
Hugo?
呃 嗨
Uh, hi.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
哇
Wow.
真是女大十八变
Uh, I wasn't expecting someone like you.
呃 你说什么?
Uh, I'm sorry?
我是说 你长得真...
You know, someone who's so...
漂亮
pretty.
快 请... 请坐
Please. H... have a seat.
你看上去都不像Rosalita了
You don't look like a Rosalita.
哦 呃 我不叫Rosalita
Oh. Um, my name isn't Rosalita.
我... 我叫Libby
I... it's Libby.
那么... 你不是我的相亲对象?
So... you're not my blind date?
不 我... 我路过这里的时候 看到了你
No, I... I just saw you from across the room.
那 你怎么知道我的名字?
Well, how'd you know my name?
呃 如果我告诉你实话 你肯定会以为我疯了
Well, if I tell you, you're gonna think I'm crazy.
不 我不会的
No, I won't.
Hugo啊
Hugo,
你相信两个人能心灵相通
do you believe that two people can be connected,
就像是灵魂伴侣么?
like soul mates?
大概吧
I guess.
你不记得我了 对么?
You don't remember me, do you?
我认识你吗?
Should I?
你在做什么 Elizabeth?
What are you doing, Elizabeth?
你在骚扰这位先生?
Are you bothering this man?
不 不 他... 他是我一个老朋友
No. No, he... he's an old friend.
事实上 我们才... 等等 这到底是... 怎么回事?
Actually, we just... Wait. What's... what's going on?
- 抱歉给您添麻烦了 我们走吧  - 不 Brooks医生 我能不能...
- I apologize for the intrusion. Come on.  - No, Dr. Brooks, if I could just...
- 医生?  - 抱歉 她刚刚离群了
- Doctor?  - I'm sorry. She just wandered off.
离什么群?
Wandered off from where?
Hugo 我说的每一件事
Everything that I said, Hugo,
都是认真的
I meant it.
抱歉打扰
Forgive us.
圣罗莎精神健康研究所
好了 我们走
All right, let's go.
夜幕降临前 我们得坐上船
We have to make it to the outriggers
- 穿过海峡 到"九头蛇"岛去  - 你弄到炸药了?
- and across the channel to Hydra Island before nightfall.  - You have the dynamite?
弄到四根...
Four sticks...
足够毁掉机舱驾驶室和所有仪器
Enough to destroy the cockpit and all the instruments.
这样一来 飞机就报废了
That plane'll never fly.
呃 我觉得这个办法不妥
Um, I don't know if that's a good idea.
我是说 这东西极不稳定
I mean, for one thing, that stuff's really unstable.
你得相信我 为这事 我早已训练良久
You have to trust me. I've been training my whole life for this.
- 就为炸东西?  - 为了保护你们
- To blow stuff up?  - To protect you.
嗯 但是炸了飞机 还怎么保护我们?
Yeah, but how is blowing up the plane protecting us?
没有飞机
With that plane gone,
- 那怪物就不能离岛了  - 对 但我们也离开不了啊
- that thing won't be able to leave the island.  - Yeah, well, neither will we,
于是我们只能和它一起被困在这儿
and then we'll be stuck here with it,
- 它会找我们麻烦的啊  - Jacob说 Richard知道该怎么做
- and it'll be angry at us.  - Jacob said Richard would know what to do.
- Richard说炸掉飞机 对吧?  - 没错
- And Richard said to blow up the plane. Correct?  - Yes.
可是 Jacob从来没这么跟我说过
Well, Jacob never said anything about it to me.
我是说 万一Richard说错了呢?
I mean, what if Richard's wrong?
Hugo 我是为你们着想 为了你们所有人
Hugo, I'm looking out for your best interests, all of you.
没什么比这更重要的了
Nothing is more important than this.
那东西是恶魔
That thing is evil,
上帝弄出这个岛 就是为了帮我们 因为...
and God help us if it ever leaves this island, because...
离地约六英尺
About six feet off the ground.
是要削根矛?
That gonna be a spear?
我也不确定 James
I'm not sure what it's gonna be yet, James.
如果削得差不多了 这东西会告诉我的
When the time is right, it'll tell me.
- 你现在跟木头谈起话来了?  - Sawyer
- You talk to wood now?  - Sawyer.
怎么了?
What?
要我为你俩做啥事么?
Something I can do for you two?
你能做什么? 把一切都搞定 如何?
Is there something you can do? How about anything?
岛那头的混蛋抓住了Jin
Those bastards on the other island grabbed Jin.
我们却坐在这里浪费时间
We're just sitting around twiddlin' our damn thumbs,
无动于衷
doin' nothin' about it.
无动于衷和耐心等待 是有区别的
There's a difference between doing nothing and waiting.
那我们在等什么?
So what are we waiting for?
你们回岛上来的唯一条件
You were only able to come back to this island
就是所有人同心协力
because you all did it together.
如果我们想登机离开
If we're gonna get on that plane and leave,
也必须这样做
it has to happen the same way.
我们等其他朋友来这儿回合 Kate...
We're waiting for your friends to get here, Kate...
比如Hugo Sun Jack...
Hugo, Sun, Jack...
只有这样
That's the only way
我们才能离开这个荒岛
we're ever getting off this godforsaken rock.
- 我可不看好这事  - 那我们走着瞧吧
- Well, I don't see that happening.  - Well, let's just hope you're wrong.
你去哪儿了?
Where you been?
我能单独和你谈谈么?
Can I speak to you in private?
当然可以
Absolutely.
一切顺利吧?
Everything go all right?
嗯
Yes.
Widmore见了你?
Did Widmore see you?
- 没 但他手下见了  - 你没杀掉他们?
- No, but his people did.  - And you let them live?
我没有杀他们的理由
I didn't see the point of killing them
- 毕竟我有事在身  - 那你弄清楚了他们藏在潜水艇上的东西 是什么吗?
- when I had what I came for.  - So you found what they were hiding in the submarine?
一清二楚
I most certainly did.
现在怎么办?
Now what?
我们得去多找些炸药 否则她就死得没意义了
We get more dynamite or else she died for nothing.
或许她的死 就是在暗示我们 别碰那些该死的炸药
Maybe she died to show us to stay the hell away from dynamite.
Jack 我倒乐意冒一冒这个险
Well, Jack, that's a risk I'm willing to take.
Richard 我答应过要带她离岛的
Richard, I promised I'd get her off this island.
Jack 我... 我希望你别这么做
Well, Jack, I... I wish you hadn't done that.
- 如果这样能让你好受些的话 你可以把责任全推到我身上  - 我认为Richard是对的
- If it makes you feel any better, you can blame it on me.  - I think Richard's right.
这是我们唯一的选择
It's the only choice we've got.
相信我 Jack
Trust me, Jack.
好吧
Okay.
好 我们走
Good. Let's get moving.
38号? 38号在吗?
38? Number 38?
Reyes先生!
Mr. Reyes!
真是太荣幸了
What an honor.
给我一个全家桶
Give me a bucket, family size.
没问题 马上就好 先生
Of course. Right away, sir.
41号?
41?
41号在吗?
Number 41?
看什么看?
What?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们以前见过吗?
Have I seen you before?
我是这儿的老板 可能你看过我的广告吧
I own the place. Maybe you saw my commercial.
莫非你想要一个"咯咯鸡"钥匙扣?
You want a clucketeer keychain?
不... 不 不是说那个
N... no. It's not that.
你坐过大洋航空的815次航班吗?
Were you on Oceanic flight 815?
- 大概一星期前 从悉尼来的那个?  - 呃 没错
- A bout a week ago, from Sydney?  - Uh, yeah.
- 我也是  - 哇 真巧啊
- So was I.  - Wow. What a coincidence.
是啊 反正我也在等着叫号 介意我跟你坐一会儿吗?
Yeah. Listen, you mind if I join you while I wait for my order?
请吧
Be my guest.
哦 好多鸡啊
Ooh. That is a lot of chicken.
- 每当沮丧的时候 我就狂吃一顿  - 啊 她叫什么名字?
- I eat when I'm depressed.  - Ah. So what's her name?
前两天我相亲的时候 遇到了一个姑娘
I met a girl on a blind date the other night.
是不是... 是不是与你想象的大相径庭?
And you didn't...  It didn't go how you'd hoped?
她美若天仙
She was totally awesome,
除了一点以外... 她疯了
expect for one thing...  she's crazy.
哥们 所有女人都有点疯狂的
Well, all women are a little bit crazy, brother.
不 她是真的疯
No. This one actually lives in the looney bin.
我看到了那个面包车 上面全是疯子
I mean, I saw the van. She's full-on nuts.
她才清醒了点儿
I mean, she started sane,
但紧接着 她就对我说 我们以前就认识...
but then she told me that we already knew each other...
至于这事么? 我有同感
And that? I'd remember.
跟我说说...
Tell me something...
她说她认识你的时候 你相信她吗?
Did you believe her when she said she knew you?
是的
Yeah.
有一点吧
Kinda.
你得跟着感觉走
You know, I say go with your gut.
或许你应该...
You know, maybe you should...
在对她绝望之前 你应该找到
you should try to find out where she thinks she knew you from
你们相识的那个地方
before you give up on her.
42号? 42号在吗?
42? Order 42?
啊 到我了 哥们
Ah, that's me, brother.
很高兴碰到你
It was nice bumping into you.
你好
Hello.
很抱歉Sayid把你绑了起来
I'm sorry Sayid tied you up,
- 他是怕 你在我们交谈之前就跑了  - 我不怪他
- But he was afraid you'd run before we had a chance to talk.  - I don't blame him.
虽然在他离开之前 我已经解释过了
Although as I explained to him before he left,
我无处可逃啊 哥们
I have nowhere to run to, brother.
这大概是我所听过的
Well, if that's not the best argument against captivity
最佳脱困词了吧
that I've ever heard,
再也找不出比这更好的了
I don't know what is.
我能问你几个问题吗 Desmond?
You mind if I ask you a couple questions, Desmond?
问吧
Not at all.
为什么Charles Widmore把你带回岛上来?
Why did Charles Widmore bring you back to the Island?
我是被绑的那个
Considering I was kidnapped,
你还是问他吧
you'd have to ask him.
他们全副武装地带着他
They had him under armed guard.
他把我扔进了一间木屋
He threw me into a wood shack
然后对我进行强力电磁场实验
and blasted me with a massive amount of electromagnetism.
希望你不介意我这么问 Desmond
If you don't mind my asking, Desmond,
你怎么知道 他对你做的实验是什么?
how can you be sure what it was that he blasted you with?
经验
Experience.
你知道我是谁吗?
Do you know who I am?
当然
Of course.
你是John Locke
You're John Locke.
回到扎营的地方 我马上回来
Head back to camp. I'll be back soon.
你要去哪儿?
Where are you going?
Desmond和我要去散散步
Desmond and I need to take a walk.
我要给你看点东西
Something I'd like to show you.
又让你若有所思了 是吧?
Kinda makes you think, doesn't it?
那是什么?
What's that?
Ilana啊
Ilana.
她就在这儿
There she was,
Jacob挑出来的
Handpicked by Jacob,
专门训练来保护你们这些接班人的
Trained to come and protect you candidates.
一旦她告诉你 你是谁的话
No sooner does she tell you who you are,
她就炸死了
then she blows up.
这座岛就随之玩完了
The Island was done with her.
所以我很想知道 如果由我们来做的话 会发生什么事情
Makes me wonder what's gonna happen when it's done with us.
好了 各位 这可能得花几分钟时间
All right, everyone. This might take a few minutes.
除了我以外 我不想让任何人来碰触这些炸药
I don't want anyone but me handling that dynamite,
所以我要一个人进去 Hugo在哪儿?
so I'm gonna go in alone. Where's Hugo?
- 我还以为他在你前面  - 快跑!
- I thought he was up front with you.  - Run!
快跑!
Run!
快跑啊!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
你干嘛要这么干啊?!
Why the hell did you do that?!
我是在保护大家啊
I'm protecting us.
- 你究竟在想什么啊?!  - 冷静点
- What the hell were you thinking?!  - Calm down.
- 现在该怎么办... 现在我们怎么办?  - 别说了 够了
- Now what... what are we supposed to do now?  - That's it. That's enough.
我们死定了 我们都死定了
We're dead. We're all dead.
至少该提前给声警报啊 Hugo
A warning might have been nice there, Hugo.
我说了"跑"的嘛
I did say "run."
为什么你要那么干?
Why'd you do that?
Michael让我这么干的
Michael told me to.
谁?
Who?
Michael啊
Michael.
有些死者 会回来冲我大喊大叫
He's one of the people who come back
他就是其中之一
and yell at me after they die.
他让我阻止大家
He told me I had to stop everyone
去炸掉飞机
from blowing up the plane.
所以... 没有炸药了 也就没有爆炸了
So... no dynamite, no more blowing up.
经常发生这事吗
That happen a lot,
死人对着你吼叫?
dead people yelling at you?
经常发生
It happens enough.
你就听从他们所说的了?
And you just listen to whatever they say?
死人比活人更可靠
Dead people are more reliable than alive people.
有什么可以帮你的吗 Reyes先生?
How can I help you, Mr. Reyes?
我想向你打听一下几天前的那个姑娘
I wanted to ask you about that girl the other day.
叫Libby的那个?
Libby?
我能不能见见她
I was wondering if maybe I could see her.
我觉得可能不行
Well, I don't think that's a good idea.
她不太舒服
She's not well.
显然 如果只是去
Clearly, she's well enough
比如... 吃个墨西哥鸡肉卷 她不会有事的
for, like, a... Fajita field trip.
那是我的错
Well, that's my mistake.
我对她的情况判断失误了
I misjudged her condition.
她的情况?
Her condition?
她认不清现实
She has issues with reality.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
我只是觉得 你现在见她
I just think it probably wouldn't be a good idea
可能不太妥当
for you to see her right now.
这只会让她更糊涂
It'll only confuse her.
你说了"可能"
You said "probably,"
就是说 可能会有例外喽
which means you might make an exception.
或许家属就没问题吧
Well, perhaps for family.
抑或是一个慷慨的捐赠者?
Or a generous donor?
什么?
I'm sorry?
我进来的时候 发现娱乐室很简陋啊
The rec room looked pretty gnarly on my way in.
你觉得十万块能买些什么呢?
What do you think 100k might buy?
你记起来了?
You remembered?
没有
No.
对不起
I'm sorry.
那你为什么来这儿?
Then why are you here?
你是在什么地方认识我的?
Where is it you think you know me from?
呃 我不知道
Um, I'm not sure.
我知道这有点讲不通
I know it won't make sense.
我...
I...
说说看嘛
Try me.
几天前 我正在看电视
A few days ago, I was watching TV,
看到了你的一则广告
and one of your commercials came on.
就在我看到你的那一瞬间
And the moment that I saw you,
我的脑袋就像是被敲了一下
It was like I was hit over the head.
我生活中的所有这些回忆
All these memories
一下次全涌现出来了...
came washing back... of my life,
只是... 这全然是...
Only... it was...
另外一种生活
another life.
什么样的回忆?
What kind of memories?
一架飞机失事了
There was a plane crash.
接着...
And...
我在一座岛上
I was on an island.
我也在那儿?
And I was there?
是的 我们就... 互相认识了
I think so. We... knew each other.
我们...
We...
喜欢上了对方
liked each other.
当我到那儿的时候
And then when I got here,
就好像我曾经来过这儿
it was almost like I'd been here before.
不知道为什么 Hugo
And for some reason, Hugo,
我记得你也来过这儿
I have a memory of you being here, too.
呃...
Um...
我是第一次来精神病院
This is the first time I've ever been in a mental hospital.
是 我知道 但你在我的脑海中挥之不去
Yeah, I know. But I can't get you out of my brain.
所以那晚我见到你的时候 我非得和你说会儿话
That's why the other night when I saw you, I had to talk to you,
因为如果你记得我的话...
because if you remembered me...
我也希望这样 Libby 但是...
I wish I could, Libby, but...
我没印象
I can't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
我疯了
I'm crazy.
可能是吧
Yeah, probably,
但... 我们都得到了一些东西 对吧?
But... we all got something, right?
我是说 去和一个陌生人说
I mean, it takes a lot of guts
你在一个奇异的平行世界里 认识他们
to go up to a total stranger and tell them you know them
是需要胆量的
from some Bizarro alternate universe.
我害怕和女孩子打招呼
I'm scared just saying "hi" to a girl.
你做得不错
You're doing fine.
嘿 你能...
Hey, can you ever, like...
离开这儿吗?
get outta here?
比如一天 或者...
On a day pass or...
是的 我是自愿来这儿的
Yeah. I'm here voluntarily.
好吧...
Well...
你想做点...
Would you like to...
什么吗?
do something?
你是说...
You mean...
约会?
a date?
嗯...
Uh...
是的
Yeah.
我愿意
I'd love that.
想一下 Desmond...
Remind me, Desmond...
你在舱底下面 按那个按钮按了多久啊?
How long were you down in that hatch, pushing that button?
三年
Three years.
现在你能又来到这里 那就更不简单了
And here you are, back for more.
要是我不清楚内情的话 我肯定会说这座岛与你有关
If I didn't know better, I'd say this island has it in for you.
你清楚内情吗?
Do you know better?
什么?
Excuse me?
我没有什么特别的 哥们
Well, there's nothing special about me, brother.
这座岛和我们大家都有关
This island has it in for all of us.
是的 没错
Yes, it does.
怎么了?
What?
那是谁?
Who's that?
别理他
Just ignore him.
- 你认识那个男孩吗?  - 我说了别理他
- Do you know that boy?  - I said ignore him.
你要去哪儿?
Where you going?
Ben 在达摩组织的营地...
Ben, back at the Dharma barracks...
还有手榴弹吗? 炸药呢?
there's still grenades there? Explosives?
- 是的 我想有吧  - 那我们就去那儿
- Yes, I think so.  - Then that's where we're going.
或许我们该谈一谈吧
Maybe we should talk about this a minute.
谈一谈? 没时间谈了 但如果你知道
Talk? There's no time to talk, but if you know
我们该做什么 如果你知道 我们除了把飞机炸毁以外
what we need to do, if you know how we stop that thing
还有别的方法 可以离开这座岛的话
from leaving the island without blowing that plane up,
- 那就让我们听听 让所有人都听听  - 我知道我们该做什么
- Then let's hear it. Let's all hear it.  - I know what we need to do.
真的? 是什么?
Really? What's that?
我们必须去找Locke谈谈了
We have to go talk to Locke.
你是想要我们大家去送死吗?
Are you trying to get us killed?
这不是我主意 是他提出来的
It's not my idea. It's his.
Jacob说 我们必须去找Locke谈谈
Jacob says we have to talk to Locke.
Jacob现在在这里吗?
Jacob's here right now?
是的
Yeah.
去问问他 这个岛是什么
Ask him what the island is.
你说什么?
What?
前段时间 Jacob曾经告诉过我这个岛是什么
A while back, Jacob told me what the island was,
如果现在他真的就在我身边
and if he's really standing here right next to me,
那就问问他呗
then just ask him.
Richard 我没有向你证明的必要
I don't have to prove anything to you, Richard.
你要么就跟我来
You either come with me
要么就继续去搞炸药
or you can keep trying to blow stuff up.
哥们 你自己决定吧
Your call, dude.
他在撒谎
He's lying.
Jacob不可能告诉我们该去做什么的
Jacob isn't telling us what to do
因为这不是他的风格
because Jacob never tells us what to do.
我还是把话说明白些吧...
I'm gonna make this simple...
如果那个东西离开了岛 那么什么都结束了
If that thing leaves the island, that's it.
- 这... 这一切都玩完了  - 什么结束了?
- It... it's over.  - What's over?
所有的一切 我会竭尽所能地
Everything. I'm destroying that plane,
去毁掉那架飞机的
and I can use all the help I can get.
谁跟我一起去?
Who's coming with me?
我
I am.
我之前见过它 哥们 可它没说话
I saw that thing in action, man. It doesn't want to talk.
对不起
Sorry.
还有别人吗?
Anyone else?
Richard 对不起
Sorry, Richard.
如果Jacob让我们去跟Locke谈 我们就得那么去做
If Jacob says we go talk to Locke, we go talk to Locke.
我会和Hugo一起的
I'm going with Hugo.
真的?
Really?
不要挡在我们前面
Don't get in our way.
好吧 Hurley
All right, Hurley.
我们去和Locke谈谈吧
Let's go talk to Locke.
我们做错了吗?
可能是
Probably.
那么 你觉得我们到那儿以后...
So what do you think we should...
应该对Locke说些什么呢?
say to Locke when we get there?
我的意思是...
I mean...
我们该如何跟这个烟怪开口说话呢?
how do you break the ice with the smoke monster?
不用为这个担心
Don't worry about it.
直觉告诉我 他会主动说话的
Something tells me he's gonna do most of the talking.
或者 他会把我们一杀了之
Or he could just kill us all.
是的 他也可能会那么做
Yeah, he could.
我在那里没有看到Jacob
I didn't see Jacob back there.
呃 我那么说 仅仅是想让大家听从我
Uh, I just said it because I wanted everyone to listen to me.
我知道的
I know.
那你为什么还跟我一起来?
Then why'd you come with me?
自从Juliet离我们而去
Ever since Juliet died,
自从她因我而死
ever since I got her killed,
我只想弥补这一切
all I've wanted was to fix it.
但是我办不到
But I can't.
我什么都弥补不了
I can't ever fix it.
你根本无法想象 我坐在那里
You have no idea how hard it is for me to sit back
听任他人吩咐 会有多么难受
and listen to other people tell me what I should do.
但我觉得可能这个是个转折点吧
But I think maybe that's the point.
可能...
Maybe...
可能我应该放手了
Maybe I'm supposed to let go.
除非你的放手 让我们俩都去送死
Unless you letting go gets us killed.
去见Locke是我的主意
Going to see Locke was my idea,
不是Jacob的
not Jacob's.
Hurley 你让我相信你
Hurley, you asked me to trust you.
我就相信你
This is me trusting you.
哎 哥们 或许这是福不是祸
Well, it's a good thing you do, dude,
因为我也不知道该怎么走
beause I have no idea where I'm going.
等等 别紧张 我知道这声音是怎么回事的
Wait. It's cool. I think I know what these things are.
喔 是吗? 这到底是什么玩意儿?
Oh, yeah? What the hell are they?
在这里等着
Wait here.
嘿 你在这里吗?
Hey. You around?
Michael呀?
Michael?
你被困在这个岛上了 对不?
You're stuck on the island, aren't you?
我罪有应得
Because of what I did.
还有...
And...
其他人也在这里...
there are others out here...
像你一样的 对吧?
like you, aren't there?
那些声音就是这样来的?
That's what the whispers are?
是的
Yeah.
我们只能待在这儿了
We're the ones who can't move on.
你知道Locke在哪里吗?
Do you know where Locke is?
在那边
There.
谢谢你
Thanks.
有...
Is...
有什么事我可以帮得上忙吗?
is there anything I can do to help you?
保住你自己的小命儿吧
Don't get yourself killed.
好的
Okay.
呃
Mm.
Hurley 帮我这个忙吧?
And, Hurley?
如果你有机会再见到Libby的话...
If you ever do see Libby again...
代我向她道歉
tell her I'm very sorry.
哥们 你就放心吧
I'll be sure and do that, dude.
我弄到了大概六种不同的芝士
I got, like, six different kinds of cheeses.
我不知道它们具体不同在哪儿
I don't even know what they are,
但是 是老板娘向我推荐的 所以就...
but the lady at the store said they were good, so...
我想既然所有人都爱吃芝士
I figured you'd like cheese
你也肯定不例外吧
because everybody likes cheese.
有啥事不对劲吗?
Is something wrong?
没 没有 只是...
No, not wrong, just...
走神了
Off.
你有来过这里吗?
Have you been here before?
没
No.
只是... 和你一起在这里 这个场景让我感到非常熟悉
It's just... being here with you feels so familiar.
像是一场梦中的约会
It's like a date we never had.
哇 听起来我像是完全疯了 对吧?
Wow. I sound completely insane, don't I?
没有
No.
只是有那么点而已
Not completely.
你为什么会想和我在一起?
Why do you even wanna be with me?
你为什么想和我在一起?
Why you wanna be with me?
你说什么?
What?
拜托
Come on.
看着我
Look at me.
我想和你在一起...
I want to be with you...
是因为我好喜欢你
because I like you.
是这样呀 但是...
Yeah, but...
你喜欢我 是因为...
you like me because...
呃 因为你有... 妄想症
well, you're... delusional.
怎么? 怎么了?
What? What's wrong?
哇哦
Whoa.
- 天呐  - 怎么了?
- Dude.  - What?
我...
I...
我想 我记起来一些事情了
I think I'm remembering stuff.
真的?
You are?
你是说我没有疯掉?
You mean I'm not crazy?
不 我才不觉得你疯了
No, I don't think you are.
我们到了
We're here.
那是什么?
What is it?
是口井
It's a well.
让我猜猜看...
Let me guess...
你现在是在想 这井会有多深
You're wondering how deep it is.
你真聪明
You read my mind.
Desmond 你可以看出这口井 建成有多久了吗?
You have any idea how old this well is, Desmond?
非常久了?
Very old?
没错 的确非常久了
That's exactly right. Very old.
事实上 这口井古老到
So old, in fact,
是挖井人
that the people who dug this well
单单用手挖成的
did it completely by hand.
天知道他们挖了多久
God knows how long it took 'em.
呃 假如仅仅是为了享受点井水 这样做未免太夸张了
Well, it seems like a lot of work just to get some water.
喔 他们不是为了井水
Oh, they weren't looking for water.
他们是在寻找答案
They were looking for answers.
很久以前
A long time ago,
比如我们现在站的这个地方
places like the one we're standing at right now
能让罗盘的指针旋转
made compass needles spin.
那些有罗盘的人
And the people holding the compasses
想知道指针为什么会转
needed to know why,
然后他们就开始挖掘
so they dug.
他们有找到答案吗?
Did they find what they were looking for?
没有 他们没有找到
No, they didn't.
Desmond 我之所以把你带到这里 看这口井
The reason I wanted you to see this, Desmond,
是因为Charles Widmore
is because Charles Widmore
他根本不在乎答案
is not interested in answers.
他只在乎权力
He's only interested in power.
他把你带回到这个岛上
And he brought you back to this island
是希望你能帮他 找到他所需要的东西
so that you could help him find what he's looking for.
毕竟 这不是唯一的井
After all, this isn't the only well.
这个就是
And that's the reason
你想让我看这口井的原因吧?
you wanted me to see this?
你为什么一点都不害怕呢?
Why aren't you afraid?
你说什么?
Excuse me?
你在这里
You're out here,
在丛林的中央
middle of the jungle,
只有我在你身旁
with me.
世上再没别人知道你在这里
Not a person on earth even knows you're here.
你为什么一点都不害怕?
Why aren't you afraid?
怕了又能怎样?
What is the point in being afraid?
啊!
Aah!
我们的朋友怎么样了?
How is our friend?
无需再挂虑他了
We don't have to worry about him anymore.
你去哪里了?
Where you been?
我就是去散了散步 James
I went for a walk, James.
既然你愿意走动了 或许你可以...
Well, now that you've stretched your legs, maybe you can...
这个混蛋
Son of a bitch.
呃... 嗨
Um... hey.
你好 Hugo
Hello, Hugo.
哥们 虽然我不知道你是谁
I don't know who you are, dude,
或者你想要什么
or what you want,
但 我们必须和你谈谈
but we have to talk to you.
"我们"?
"We"?
还有另外一些人跟着我呢
There are other people with me.
目前的情况是
But the thing is,
你我都拥有武器
you got weapons, and we got weapons,
而我不想有任何人受伤...
and I don't want anyone to get hurt...
或是遇害
or killed.
所以我们不会采取任何行动
So we're not gonna do anything,
我希望你能向我保证 你也不会采取任何行动
and I want your word that you're not gonna do anything either.
我向你保证
You have my word.
好了 伙伴们
Okay, guys.
都出来吧
Come on out.
你好 Jack
Hello, Jack.
你好
Hello there.
你是在等什么人吗?
Are you waiting for someone in particular?
怎么了?
Excuse me?
是这样 我注意到 你在这里很久了
Well, I noticed you've been parked here a while,
一直看着那些孩子 还有 呃 这里是所学校
watching the kids, and, well, it is a school.
你有孩子在这里上学吗?
Do you have a child who goes here?
没 没有 我只是 呃
No. No. I was, um,
呃 我刚刚才搬到这里的
uh, I just moved to the neighborhood,
我 呃 我 呃 我想给我儿子找个学校
and, um, and, uh, I'm looking for a school for my son.
- 你儿子叫什么呀?  - Charlie
- What's your son's name?  - Charlie.
作为这里的一名老师 我可以拍胸脯保证
Well, as a teacher here, I can vouch for it completely.
这是所非常好的学校
It's a wonderful school.
谢谢你的建议 谢谢你
That's great to hear. Thanks.
很开心见到你
Well, it was nice talking to you.
祝你有愉快的一天
Have a good day.
呃... 呃
Mm... hmm.
哇!
Oh!
报警呀! 赶紧的!
Call 911! Do it now!
Locke先生?
Mr. Locke?
喔 我的天呐
Oh, my God.
别... 别动 我们马上送你去医院
Don't... don't move. We're gonna get you to the hospital.
Locke先生?
Mr. Locke?
Locke先生 你可以听到我说话吗?
Mr. Locke, can you hear me?